12 years ago a nine-tailed fox and Lee appeared its tails lashed out smashing mountains and sending title waves crashing to the shores the ninja rose up to defend their villages.
It's getting closer don't want to do.
Once you know these face the nine-tailed fox in Mortal Kombat.
Sacrificed his life to capture the Beast and steals in a human body was known as the fourth Hokage.
You're just mad because you don't have the guts to do what I do. Want to beat you never text me. It's an emergency. I hope you're not bothering me with some trivia and don't tell me it's not Ruto again.
That was too easy.
You come for me we could then say what are you doing here? What are you doing here? You're supposed to be in class.
I'm at the end of my rope Naruto. You failed the graduation test last time and the time before that tomorrow. You got another chance and you're messing up again.
transformed into me
Sasuke Uchiha
Naruto Uzumaki, Naruto
Like I care.
transform
sexy Jutsu
Loser, you're not going home till you cleaned up every single drop of pee.
I like there's anyone waiting at home for me.
Naruto
What do you want now since a I was just thinking maybe after you clean this all up I could take you out for some rum the good stuff. What do you think?
Look up some serious motivation to clean and no time.
picture of Naruto Uzumaki
Naruto
Why would you do that? Cuz I Hokage faces. I mean, you know who the Hokage are don't you?
Everybody knows they were the greatest Shinobi of your time write the best of the best undefeated ninja Champs.
And the fourth Hokage is the one who saved the Village from the nine-tailed fox. He was the most amazing. Why did you because I'm going to be greater than any of them me Naruto the next Hokage ninja legend that everyone will have to stop disrespecting me and look talk to me believe it. By the way. I don't want to ask a little favor Sensei another Bowl
I want to trade in your headband. Come on, please. You can only wear the leaf headband when you finally graduate from the academy and become a ninja you've got to pass the test tomorrow.
Is that why you took off your goggles?
We will now start the final exam when your name is called proceed to the testing room. The final test will be on the Clone Jutsu.
That's my word technique. I'm never going to pass.
Get it together Naruto. You can do this and leave it.
iruka sensei
He's off but his moves weren't bad and he did hang in there and replicate this is his third try so, you know, he really wants to become a ninja we could cut him a break or passing Mizuki Sensei the other students created at least three effective replications.
But Naruto could only create one and look at it. It's pitiful. I can't pass him.
big deal appliances
I wish your grandma would say I'm proud of you son. We all are.
Bear him only one who failed ninja and heat the boy who we're not allowed to talk about that.
Alright your ruca.
Oh, I think he will something we need to talk about.
If you can Simpsons tapped out, but he's not against you.
He wants you to be strong with all his heart, but that will never happen if he goes easy on you. He's like you you know, no parents. No family this time. I really wanted to graduate. I guess I have to tell you a secret.
arouca
What is it Lord Hokage? I know how you feel you grew up just like Naruto without knowing the love of a mother and father the Warren Family.
It's getting closer. Don't let it near the field.
Wake up.
What what is it? You need to come to load hokages right away. It's not Ruto.
He told the secret feelings no.
Ritzy, the first one is the multi Shadow clone Jutsu.
This is a serious by the First Hokage secret. I could destroy our entire way of life.
All right. Bring Naruto here at 1.
Now that I told everyone was eliminated.
And of course I can control for myself.
It's all over.
You're quick Sensei. I only had time to learn one technique has been working.
Listen to bukit and say I'm going to show you this amazing just do and you're going to let me graduate then everything will be okay. That's the way it works. Right anyone learn to Justin from the scroll past is present you sent. I told me about it. He told me where to find a straw and this place.
I see you found our little Hideaway. So that's the way it is. I should have known.
Naruto give me the scroll now.
What's going on here?
Don't make me to get the scroll.
Naruto has just trying to scare you cuz he doesn't want you to have the scroll.
Lying me to KI don't let him treat you now since the tree 12 years ago.
Free everyone knows it. You could try and hide it from you even now he do anything. What is this degree? Why is everyone else you know about it didn't agree is no one can tell you the nine-tailed Fox's inside you.
Spiritually rooted parents and destroyed our village is taking over your body. You are the nine-tailed fox.
They've all been around.
Naruto that's why you will never be a father to care for him out of everything and doesn't know why most people won't even look at him. How would you feel it everywhere? You went people turn their backs on you. That's why he gets in trouble. So people will notice him. It may not show but he's always thinking about the family. He doesn't have he's hurting inside.
Naruto Naruto
Why?
Because we're the same when I lost my parents no one seemed to care. They didn't have time for me. I just forgot I was there my grades I became the class clown. I just wanted them to see me and to know my name. My schoolwork wasn't good enough to get their attention. So I do crazy things that I had to pay for.
It was hard. I know that's how you feel about her.
You feel lonely and it hurts inside and I could have been there for you more. I let you down. I'm sorry. No one should have to suffer that much. No one should be alone Mike.
50 50 50 50 make me laugh. He say anything to get the scroll for you.
You know once he makes up his mind nothing can change him. He's going to use this girl to take revenge on the village.
You saw that look in his eyes and you those are the eyes of the Beast.
is flight
Give me a joke. As soon as I limited Naruto to get the scroll. I'll be back for you.
This is not good music. He has a big mouth. He made Naruto feel so bad the power inside of him Naruto keeps tampering with a scroll the steel that locks the fox spirit inside of him to be broken and the Beast could come out if that happens. What I saw.
Naruto everything Mizuki said was a lie. Give me the 12:30 to take it away.
How did you know how did you know that it was me and not a hookah?
I forgot you're a fool. Why are you protecting at Greek? He's the one that wiped out your family. I don't care what you say. You're not getting your hands on that scroll. You can stop me to get it Naruto is just like me.
How's that he wants to scroll through his own power and his own invention that helped East. Are you pour all his rage into the scroll and destroyed everything?
light
through thick and thin never believe me. He thinks I'm some beat some kind of
Quinta B Star
but that's not who Naruto is. He's nothing like that. Naruto is one-of-a-kind works hard puts his whole heart into it. Sometimes suffering only makes me stronger. That's what separates him from being a feast. So you're wrong. He's nothing like the nine-tailed fox Village hidden in the leaves.
You really believe that turtle.
Naruto
you ever lay a hand on my sweet destroy you with a single mom.
Take Your Best Shot. Do you a thousandfold show me what you can do tonight?
This solid clones. He's mastered and extremely Advanced Chute system.
If you're not coming, so we're going to come after you.
Sorry, I kind of got carried away you okay? We're cuz then say he wants to surpass all the time and I'm starting to believe he might do it.
Give me a redneck. I've got something I want to give you.
No, one can find Naruto.
Not a clue bad news. We got to smoke him out or something. It was no longer any need to
Let's Roll safe Naruto be back soon.
How much longer you can open your eyes now?
Congratulations you graduate.
And to celebrate I have a surprise. We're going out for ramen tonight.
Naruto this is only the beginning the road gets tougher now that you're a ninja but if I told you that I guess it would ruin the moment. So I'll tell you when you're older Ramen.
selfie, Indiana
Why are you following me? Do you want to become the fifth Hokage? Listen up you little shrimp. I don't care if you want to go potty grandson. I can't just snap your fingers and become a top ninja you better be ready for work. Cuz if you even think about being a Hokage, you'll have to be paid first next time. My name is cut on roof.